visitnc.com 2015-06-29

# Privacy | VisitNC.com

Visit North Carolina is committed to protecting your privacy on this website.

We collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis only. Personal information may include name, address, phone number, email address and other relevant data. We do not require this personal information to obtain access to most of our site.

We do, however, require it in order to properly respond or to fulfill requests for the following:

  * Brochures or other mailed information
  * Email newsletters
  * Sweepstakes entries
  * Saving personalized Trip Planner itineraries and folders
  * Sharing your opinions through surveys
  * Using Contact Us for correspondence
  * Submitting an RFP for Group Tour Planning

We do not share email addresses you provide us when you use the email-a-friend feature. When you contact us via email, we will only use the information to respond to your request. We may occasionally redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question.

###  Public Disclosure

The personal information we request is used by us in order to process a request for information by you or for marketing our products or services. We do not collect, track, sell or rent personal information to other organizations.

If you provided us with personal information through this web site, you have the option to request that we not contact you in the future. If you allow us to contact you in the future, Visit North Carolina’s tourism partners and businesses may provide you with current and future information about travel opportunities in the state of North Carolina. Information about you or your requests will not be shared with any other organizations.

###  What Information Do We Collect?

Our web servers collect the domain names, but not the email addresses, of visitors to our website. This information is aggregated to measure number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, and other relevant statistics.

We collect the following information: 

  * The Internet domain and IP address from which you access our site
  * The date and time you access our site
  * The length of time you spend on our site
  * The pages you visit
  * The URL of the site you came from, if applicable

We collect this information to measure the use of our site, to improve the content of our site, to evaluate technical performance and to identify problem areas.

###  Cookies

To enhance your experience on our site, many of our web pages use cookies. Cookies are small text files that we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. Once you choose to provide a web page with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. A cookie is like an identification card. It is unique to your computer and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to provide you tailored offers of products and services. Cookies are essential to the proper functioning of VisitNC.com.

If you want to control which cookies you accept, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a website’s server offers a cookie. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser.

###  Video Privacy

The videos produced by Visit North Carolina are designed to display some of the wonderful places, events, and scenery of North Carolina. People shown in the video features were filmed enjoying North Carolina's public places or filmed on private property with the full permission of the property owner. Their appearance in the video does not constitute actual or implied endorsement of Visit North Carolina.

###  Disclaimer

Visit North Carolina has compiled content and information contained in this site based on data provided by local tourism partners and business entities. While every effort is made to ensure the accuracy of this information, Visit North Carolina makes no representations, guarantees or warranties as to the accuracy, completeness or suitability of the information provided on this web site. All data is subject to change without notice. Travelers are advised to contact individual businesses or organizations to obtain the most current information before traveling.

The VisitNC.com website contains links to other sites and we attempt to only link to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. Links to third-party websites are provided as a convenience for our site visitors and do not constitute endorsement or control of their content.

###  Copyright

© 2015 Visit North Carolina.

###  Contact Information

Additional questions or concerns about these policies should be directed to the [contact page at VisitNC.com](http://www.visitnc.com/contactus).

See something wrong?

Tell us about it.

Go with the flow and see where the water takes you from the scenic Riverwalk lined with shops and cafes to the family-friendly entertainment found on…

When you think of extraordinary golf, the Pinehurst area, also known as the “Home of American Golf”, often immediately comes to mind. Full of…
